zehabesha.com 2019-06-23

# Zehabesha – Latest Ethiopian News Provider | Privacy Policy

### **Legal Disclaimer**

This website is owned and operated by the Zehabesha.com for public online news consumption, Health Education. Accessing to any portion of this website or by using any portion of this website, you agree to be bound by terms and conditions. Please review our other policies, such as our privacy policy and our data gathering policy,  type of information that ZeHabesha gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive our News updates via email, we collect their emails. For example, when you to sign up for an account, we ask for personal information, like your name, email address. When visitors comment on our blog, we ask them to provide a username and email address. These policies also govern your use of this website. If you do not agree to be bound by these terms and conditions, do not proceed any further and do not use this website. We recommend printing a copy of this page for your reference. We also recommend referring back to this document regularly, as we may make changes and post them to this website.

### **Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to us, at ZeHabesha we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site. It is Zehabesha’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### **Visitors   Policy**

Like most website operators, ZeHabesha collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ZeHabesha’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ZeHabesha’s visitors use its website. From time to time, ZeHabesha may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. ZeHabesha also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. ZeHabesha only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left. Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.

### **Cookies  Policy**

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ZeHabesha, cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Our policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Comments and other content submitted to Disqus anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

### **Comments   Policy**

We love comments and appreciate the time that our readers spend to share ideas and give feedback. Comments and other content submitted to Disqus anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

### **Terms & conditions**

ZeHabesha has the right at any time to change or discontinue any aspect or feature of the website, including, without limitation, the content, hours of availability, and equipment needed for access or use of the website. Use of this Website is solely at ZeHabesha.com’s discretion, and ZeHabesha.com reserves the right to prohibit anyone from accessing, browsing, supplying information to, downloading information from, or conducting business on this website.

The website contains copyrighted material, trademarks and other proprietary information, including, without limitation, text, software, photos, video, graphics, music and sound. The contents of the website are copyrighted under the United States copyright laws and international treaties (“Information”). You are not granted any rights in  or to this website or any Information, other than the limited right described in these terms and conditions and any policies and procedures that Zehabesha.com may adopt and make available on this website from time to time, including the Privacy Policy below.

The Information may be supplied by Zehabesha.com or third parties and users of the website. Any opinions, advice, statements, or other information or content expressed or made available by third parties are those of the respective author(s) or distributor(s) and not of Zehabesha.com. In many instances, the content available through the website represents the opinions and judgments of the respective information provider or user. Zehabesha.com neither endorses nor is responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice or statement made on the website by anyone other than authorized Zehabesha.com spokespersons acting in their official capacities.

If you provide Information to Zehabesha.com for posting on the website, you grant to Zehabesha.com and its successors and assigns a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, distribute, create derivative works of, display, and broadcast that Information; and authorize specified third parties to use, reproduce, distribute, download, create derivative works of and print such Information for their own internal business purposes. You agree that Zehabesha.com shall be free to use any ideas, concepts or techniques contained in your Information for any and all proper purposes.

While it may monitor, remove or delete transmissions to this website, Zehbesha.com is under no obligation to monitor, remove or delete any transmissions. Zehabesha.com exercises no editorial review and assumes no responsibility for misleading, fraudulent, defamatory, libelous, threatening, harassing, pornographic, obscene or illegal Information supplied to this website; provided, however, that Zehabesha.com may take any action with respect to any Information that Zehabesha.com deems in its sole discretion is necessary or appropriate, including the deletion of any such Information.

This website may provide links to other Internet sites. Such links are provided as a service to users and are not sponsored by, endorsed or otherwise affiliated with this website or with the products and services of Zehabesha.com. Zehabesh.com is not responsible for the availability of such other sites and is not responsible or liable for any content, products or other materials available on such other sites. Further, Zehabesha.com reserves the right to terminate any link at any time. Zehabesha.com does not author, edit, or monitor these unofficial pages or links. You acknowledge and agree that Zehabesha.com shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any information, goods or services available on or through any such website. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this website, you do this entirely at your own risk.

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold Zehabesha.com harmless from and against any damage, loss, liability or expense (including reasonable attorney’s fee) that Zehabesha.com may suffer or incur as a result of any claim attributable to or based upon your use of this website or any of the Information. If for any reason you are not satisfied with this website or the Information, your sole remedy is to cease using this website or the Information.

If any provision of these terms and conditions is held to be unenforceable, this holding will not affect the validity of the other provisions. Zehabesha.com controls and operates this website from our home in Minnesota. These terms and conditions, and your use of the website, will be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of Minnesota, U.S.A.

Zehabesha.com may change these terms and conditions from time to time and at any time, without actual notice to you. In the event of a change, Zehabesha.com will post the revised version to our web website, any access to or use of the website after such an update will be deemed consent to such update.

ZeHabesha Website is not responsible for accuracy of information or endorses the contents provided by external sources. All blog posts and comments are the opinion of the authors.

Copyright © 2013 [Zehabesha – Latest Ethiopian News Provider](http://www.zehabesha.com/ "Latest Ethiopian News Provider"). All Rights Reserved.
